# Shubham Tiwary

Kolkata, West Bengal, India



shubhamtiwary@outlook.in



linkedin.com/in/tiwaryshubham

# Summary

I am a passionate Student Developer and have a very sharp interest towards Data Science and Full Stack Development. Also, I am a Graphic Designer, Illustrator and a writer who loves to tangle with literary tropes.

Apart from these, I work hard to augment my area of expertise by learning new skills and getting better at my existing ones. I strongly believe that what challenges us are the ones that changes us.

https://shubhamtiwary.xyz/

# Experience



# Website Manager

Government College of Engineering and Textile Technology, Berhampore

Feb 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months +)

Actively managing and fixing bugs for the College Website and working on an alternate College Alumni Connect Web App

# Chief Editor and Designer for The Reminiscence 2K18 Magazine - Souvenir for The Reminiscence 2K18

Government College of Engineering and Textile Technology, Berhampore

Jan 2019 - May 2019 (5 months)

Wrote various articles about the event and edited the articles posted. Designed the layout and graphics of the magazine which focused every detail of the event

# Graphic Designer

Government College of Engineering and Textile Technology, Berhampore

Nov 2018 - Jan 2019 (3 months)

Chief Animateur and Graphic Designer for The Reminiscence 2K18 Event - hosted by GCETTB to felicitate the Alumni Members of the College

#### **Education**



#### Government College of Engineering and Textile Technology, Berhampore

B. Tech, Computer Science & Engineering

2018 - 2022



### Jermel's Academy, Silliguri

All India Senior School Certificate Examination (Class - XII), PCM

# St. Xavier's School, Siliguri

Indian Certificate of Secondary Education Examination (Class - X)

# **Licenses & Certifications**

Machine Learning using Python - WebSkitters Academy



Introduction to Self Driving Cars - University of Toronto

FAL8CEMBY5XV

**G** Technical Support Fundamentals - Google

**KYNESHEFA3E5** 

**G** Crash Course on Python - Google

MEBVH94TPPKT

# **Skills**

Python (Programming Language) • Android Development • C • Java • CorelDRAW • C++ • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5 • HTML • JavaScript